Usage: odavl <command>
Commands:
  scan           Outputs placeholder HealthSnapshot JSON
  heal           Fix code issues (--recipe remove-unused, --apply)
  branch create  Create a new git branch
  pr open        Open a pull request (--explain, --dry-run, --title)
  shadow run     Trigger CI workflow (--ref <branch>, --wait, --dry-run)
  shadow status  Check CI workflow status (--ref <branch>, --watch)
  status         Show current project status (branch, governor, telemetry, CI)
  governor explain  Show current governor status for PR and shadow operations
  report telemetry summary  Show usage analytics (--since 24h|<ISO>)
  undo last      Restore files from last heal --apply (--show to preview)
  abort          Cancel in-progress GitHub Actions runs on current branch
